(Leonard:)Pass the soy sauce.
(Amy:)Bernadette just asked about
my sexual encounter with you.
(Amy:)The meme has reached
full penetration.
(Sheldon:)Pun intended?
(Amy:)No. Happy accident.
(Sheldon:)This is remarkable.
(Sheldon:)Took less than 24 hours.
(Amy:)I should let you know
(Amy:)that she asked for details
about our dalliance.
(Amy:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)So it went beyond the
mere fact of coitus
to a "blow by blow,"
as it were.
(Sheldon:)Pun intended?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry. What pun?
(Amy:)Not important.
(Amy:)I described your lovemaking
as "aloof, but effective."
(Sheldon:)I wish you hadn't done that.
(Sheldon:)That's going to make
me a chick magnet,
(Sheldon:)and I'm so busy as it is.
(Howard:)Hey, everybody,